(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-11T21:39:45.114639",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ご来場のお客様へ：演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
To venue attendees: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Loud cheering is OK!
だから
That's why...
君のこと 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れるこの
This overflowing...
愛が
...love...
きっと 止まらない
...surely won't stop!
I I I I I love you
I-I-I-I-I love you!
あいあいあいあい♡
I I I I...
あいにじゅー
I need you!
もっと (もっと) 好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want, more and more!
揺れるハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My wavering heart goes bounce, bounce, bounce!
穴に落ちて あびゃびゃ
Falling into a hole, completely helpless!
こんなになっても未だ抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't break free!
どうしたもんかね ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui nui nui!
助けてきみたち アホイホイ
Save me, everyone! Ahoy, hoy!
もっと (もっと!) もっと (もっと!)
More (more!) More (more!)
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
どアニメ宣言！
Do Anime Sengen!
アニメにハマって
I fell in love with anime...
歌いたくなっちゃった
...and now I really want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら
While watching my favorite scenes...
カラオケ歌えるなんて
...being able to sing karaoke...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
...is so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニソン・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let me find the anime and game songs I want to sing!
どアニメ宣言！
Do Anime Sengen!
吉野家でごはんしょ♪
Let's eat at Yoshinoya♪
ぎゅう〜
Beefy~
ぎゅうぎゅう
Beefy, beefy
ぎゅう〜
Beefy~
うまっ！
Delicious!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Taste the true commitment of the original.
牛丼は吉野家
For beef bowls, it's Yoshinoya.
今日も吉野家日和です。
Today is another perfect day for Yoshinoya.
本日は
Today,
ホロライブ
hololive...
サードジェネレーションライブ
3rd Generation Live,
キルルン大作戦
Operation Kirurun:
最強アイドル お推ししかないでしょに
The Strongest Idols, Push 'Em All The Way!
ご来場いただき ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming today!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために
To ensure you enjoy the live show until the very end,
いくつかご案内させていただきます。
we have a few announcements to make.
公演中の撮影、録音、
Photography, audio recording,
録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
and video recording during the show are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は
In the event that you feel unwell,
無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
please do not push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、
Moshing,
ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
stage diving, throwing objects onto the stage,
他のみんなの迷惑になったり
or any actions that cause trouble for others
公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
or disrupt the performance are strictly forbidden.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and enjoy the show!
あー、聞こえるね！聞こえるね！うん！
Ah, I can hear you! I can hear you! Yep!
また、本公演は
Also, for this concert,
映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
video streaming and photography cameras are in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合があります。
and audience members may appear in the footage.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください！
These images and footage may be used for promotional purposes, so please be aware of this in advance!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは
Also, the concert's official hashtag is
「#キルルン大作戦 Day2」です！
"#KirurunDaisakusen Day2"!
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくだい！
Please use the hashtag to share your excitement!
それでは、開演まであと少しです！
Well then, it's just a little while until the show starts!
君たちの声をいっぱい聞かせてください！
Please let us hear your voices loud and clear!
そして！
And now...
今からちょっと3期生で円陣を組もうと思っているんですが...
Us 3rd gen members are about to form a huddle...
マイクを通さずやりますので、
We're going to do it without our microphones,
ちょっと静かにして、耳を澄ませていただけますか？
so could you please quiet down and listen closely?
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much!
行くんで、ちょっとシーンと待っててね。
Here we go, so please wait quietly, okay?
静かにね。
Shh, quiet now.
3期生...
3rd Generation...
行くぞー！
Let's do this!
おー！
Yeah!
超アイドル 電脳ガールズ 欲張り
Cyber girls who are ultimate idols, so greedy,
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
smiling together makes us even cuter.
Oh yeah yeah
問わないよ 年齢格差
Age gap doesn't matter,
他人なのに家族みたいで
we're strangers, yet like family.
ラブのグラデーション クルラダイセッション
A gradation of love, a cool live session,
喜怒哀楽をシェアしてさ
sharing all our emotions with you.
でっかくなっていきたいよね！ でもちっちゃなことも大事にして
We want to get bigger! But let's cherish the little things too.
ひとつひとつ
Step by step,
重ねていく 楽しんでくれるのが楽しい！
building them up. Seeing you enjoy it is what makes us happy!
だから応援してーな
So please keep cheering for us!
後ろだって見えてる
We can see all the way to the back!
画面の向こうも届いてる
Reaching out beyond the screen too!
光の海を泳ぐの
Swimming through a sea of lights!
超アイドル 電脳ガールズ 欲張り
Cyber girls who are ultimate idols, so greedy,
愛されたいし 夢の君と君とじゃなきゃ イヤだ！
we want to be loved, and if it's not with you and you in our dream, no way!
絶好調です！
In peak condition!
狙い撃ちで君にウィンク
Aiming right at you with a wink!
やっぱ電脳ガールで めっちゃハッピー
Being cyber girls makes us so super happy after all!
あれもしたいし これもしたいし 叶っちゃう！
We want to do this and that, and our wishes are coming true!
先頭走る 夢中な君と
Running at the front with you who's fully absorbed,
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
smiling together makes us even cuter.
Oh yeah yeah
全国だからやり切りたい！ でも乗り越えるべき壁もデカイ
It's nationwide, so we want to give it our all! But the walls to overcome are huge too.
将来性？ エンターテインメント！
Future potential? Entertainment!
みんなを笑顔にできるようずっと
So that we can bring smiles to everyone, always...
君のこと思ってる
thinking of you.
どうかな？
How about it?
焦がれた夢に近づけてるかな？
I wonder if I'm getting closer to the dream I longed for?
いろんなことがあるから頑張れるんだ 聞かせて！
Because so much happens, I can keep working hard, so let me hear you!
超最高 電脳ガールズ 幸せ
Cyber girls who are super best, so happy,
愛されていて 乗り越えて 下向くとか イヤだ！
being loved, overcoming obstacles, looking down is... no way!
テンポアップして 続けていく
Speeding up the tempo, keeping it going,
見たことない景色へ
toward a sight we've never seen before!
世界にダッシュで
Dashing out into the world!
世界より大冒険！
A grand adventure bigger than the world!
今すぐ達成！
Achieving it right now!
みんなで作っていく！
Creating it all together with everyone!
どこまでも盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's keep pumping up the energy to the limit!
君たち、まだまだ声出せますよねー！
You guys can still make some noise, right?!
嫌いでも
Even if you dislike it,
がんばっちゃう
I'll still do my best.
褒められて伸びるわかってるよね？
You know I thrive on praise, right?
本能感が宝物
Our instincts are a treasure,
変わらないや
and that won't change.
君と一緒に！
Together with you!
超アイドルなガールは欲張り
Super idol girls are greedy.
愛されたいし 夢見てみたい 君とじゃなくっちゃ
We want to be loved and dream big—it has to be with you!
野望絶好調です
Our ambitions are at their peak!
願い打ち抜いて
Shoot right through our wishes,
君にウインク
here's a wink for you!
やっぱ
After all,
超アイドルなガールでめちゃハッピー
being a super idol girl makes me so happy!
あれもしたいし これもしたいし 叶っちゃう
I want to do this and that, and it all comes true!
先頭走る もちろん君と
Running at the front, of course with you,
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
laughing together and becoming even cuter!
どこまででもいけちゃう気がする
I feel like we can go anywhere!
Oh yeah yeah!
今日はこのままサヨナラじゃないよ
Today doesn't end in a goodbye like this.
手を取ってくれたなら
If you take my hand...
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に
...on a night where even secrets fall asleep,
君を連れて行くよ
I will take you along.
それはたとえば遠く離れていたって
Even if we were far apart,
手をつないでいられるような奇跡のような
like a miracle where our hands remain linked,
話をしよう 窓を開けておいて
let's talk. Keep your window open.
今日までを思い出して
Thinking back on everything up to today,
ひとつひとつ並べたら
when I line them up one by one,
明日の雨が気になりだして
I start worrying about tomorrow's rain,
どうも眠れないみたいだ
and it seems I just can't sleep.
変わりたくないことや
The things I don't want to change,
変わらなきゃいけないことも
and the things that must change...
少し忘れたまま
Forgetting them just for a moment,
窓の外 眺めていたんだ
I was gazing outside the window.
雨が降り出すその前に
Before the rain begins to fall,
君のところまでいけるような気がして
I feel like I can reach where you are,
目を閉じてみたんだ
so I closed my eyes.
このまま遠くへへといこう
Let's go far away like this.
手を取ってくれるかな
Will you hold my hand?
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
Through a night where even secrets fall asleep,
君と泳いでいくよ
I will swim through it with you.
街の明かりが消えるたびに笑って
Laughing every time the city lights go out,
路地裏で抱き合おう
let's embrace in the alleyway.
バカみたいな話をしよう
Let's talk about silly things.
窓を開けておいて
Keep your window open.
きこえる
Can you hear it?
次はマリン！
Next up is Marine!
キミたちー！3期生ライブ盛り上がっていくよー！
Everyone~! Let me see your energy for 3rd Gen live~!
言うの？マリン！
You want Marine?!
どっちが好きかなんて言わなくてもわかるよ！
Even if you don't say who you like better, I already know!
どっちが好きなのよ！
Which one of us do you like?!
何とかなんないかな
Can't something be done about this?
隣のアイツが邪魔だな
The one next to me is in the way!
行くなー！そんなこと！
Don't say things like that!
ダメダメだ！全力必勝！絶対！
No way, no way! Full power victory, guaranteed!
根本的に違った なんの競争？
We're completely different, what kind of competition is this?
意味が出たそれよな
Does that even make sense?
なんの何に？ どっち？どっち？
What for? Which one? Which one?
あっちも負けられない こっちだって譲らない 欲張りね 横取りか？ してやります！
Neither side will lose, nor step back! Greedy, huh? Stealing the spotlight? I'll do it!
言わなきゃ分かってる
I know without you having to say it.
あーでもない
It's not like this,
こーでもない やめにしましょう
nor like that—let's just stop.
釣られるけど
Even if I get pulled in...
My my my my!
引き出せない
...can't bring it out!
言い訳ばかり
Nothing but excuses,
違いだの優柔不断
differences and indecisiveness.
段々ハニバニになりたり
Gradually becoming a honey bunny...
マジな話 どっち？どっち？
Seriously though, which one? Which one?
が好きなのよ！
...do you like?!
よそ見しないで！
Don't look away!
アピール出したいの
I want to show off my charm!
は私の方
That's on my side!
どっちにして？
Which one will you choose?!
反対方向
In opposite directions!
言わなきゃに
Unless you speak up...
尽きることない言い訳ばかり
Nothing but endless excuses,
ズボラだの優柔不端だの
calling me lazy or indecisive.
ハニワになりたや マジな話
Seriously, I just want to turn into a Haniwa.
ボッチ ぼっち 孤独が好きなのよ
Loner, loner, I like being alone!
ダメダメダメ
No, no, no,
よそ見しないで
don't look away!
ダメダメダメ
No, no, no,
もう抜け出したい
I want to break free already!
でもやるしかない
But I've got no choice,
正面突破で
a frontal breakthrough!
反対方向
In the opposite direction,
ワンターン！
one turn!
言い訳ばかり
Nothing but excuses,
そばに居て言い訳ばかり
even right beside you, nothing but excuses.
あー
Ah~
次はペコラー！
Next up is Pekora~!
全力ジャンプ いくぺこー！
Full power jump, here we go, peko~!
イエーイ！
Yayy!
どこへ行こうか 計画ナシで
Where shall we go, with no plans?
歌いながら気の向く方へ
Sing along wherever our hearts take us!
迷ってるの？
Are you lost?
冒険してるの？
Are you on an adventure?
それはみんな次第！
That's all up to everyone!
まだまだ楽しみ足んない
Still haven't had enough fun,
でもでも時間が足んない
but there's still not enough time!
ワクワクする明日へ
Toward an exciting tomorrow,
思い切って張り切って前向いて
take the plunge, give it your all, look ahead!
さあ、進もう！
Come on, let's move forward!
せーのっ！
Ready, set, go!
いつだって本気で！
Always with all our heart!
遊び尽くしちゃえ！
Play to our heart's content!
やりすぎちゃうくらいで
To the point of overdoing it,
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
it's all okay!
早起きよりも徹夜にしちゃおう
Let's stay up all night instead of waking up early!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから！
Because everything will turn out fine somehow!
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
A pinch turns into an opportunity,
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
it's all okay!
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
When we all laugh together, we're invincible!
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all okay!
なんだって全力で！
Give everything our all!
突き抜けちゃって！
Break right through!
真っ直ぐな気持ちでいこう！
Let's go with straightforward feelings!
ホップ ステップ ジャンプで 飛び出そう！
Hop, step, jump, let's leap forward!
なかなかお布団から
On days when I can hardly get out
出られない日もある
from under the futon,
でも明日から そう明日から
but starting tomorrow, yes, starting tomorrow,
本気をだすんだ！
I'll give it my all!
気が済むまで！
Until I'm satisfied!
日が暮れるまで！
Until the sun sets!
門限なんか無視で
Ignoring any curfew,
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
it's all okay!
早起きよりも徹夜にしちゃおう
Let's stay up all night instead of waking up early!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから！
Because everything will turn out fine somehow!
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
A pinch turns into an opportunity,
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
it's all okay!
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
When we all laugh together, we're invincible!
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all okay!
なんだって全力で！
Give everything our all!
突き抜けちゃって！
Break right through!
真っ直ぐな気持ちでいこう！
Let's go with straightforward feelings!
ホップ ステップ ジャンプで 飛び出そう！
Hop, step, jump, let's leap forward!
イエーイ！
Yayy!
最後はノエルー！
Last up is Noel~!
はい！みんなシャッフルメドレー最後まで盛り上がっていくぞー！
All right, everyone! Let's heat up this shuffle medley until the very end!
苦い恋の果て
At the end of a bitter romance,
残された Dead or Cold
left behind with a Dead or Cold,
不運な鐘の音
the sound of an unlucky bell.
あいつの気配がするものは
Things that carry his presence
未練ばかりで食えやしない
are full of regrets and totally indigestible.
あたしは生きながら
While I'm still alive,
化けて出る
I'll return as a ghost.
鏡の前で早変わり
A quick change in front of the mirror,
パイパイ仮面でどうかしら
how about turning into PaiPai Kamen?
今宵もひと暴れ
Going wild once again tonight!
踊れ 踊り 踊れ
Dance, dance, dance!
乱れ髪 跳ねる胸
Disheveled hair, bouncing chest,
匿名之罠に酔いしれて
drunk on the trap of anonymity!
シャイヤッポ！ シャイヤッポ！ シャイヤッポ！ ライトミーアップ！
Shaiyappo! Shaiyappo! Shaiyappo! Light me up!
パイ！ パパイ！ パパパパイ！
Pai! Papai! Papapapai!
パイパイ仮面は大苦戦
PaiPai Kamen is in a tough fight!
パイ！ パパイ！ パパパパイ！
Pai! Papai! Papapapai!
黄金の夜 舞い上がれ
Soar through the golden night!
踊れよ 散財万歳 恋のシャワー
Dance! Long live extravagance, shower of love!
刹那を生きてよ
Live for the moment,
瞬間クライマックス
an instant climax!
浮世 忘れて耽る
Forget the fleeting world and indulge,
ダンシングハイ
dancing high!
パイ！ パパイ！
Pai! Papai!
ディスコティックに
Discotheque style!
パイパイ仮面
PaiPai Kamen!
パイ！ パパイ！ パパパパイ！
Pai! Papai! Papapapai!
パイパイ仮面は大苦戦
PaiPai Kamen is in a tough fight!
パイ！ パパイ！
Pai! Papai!
ハイ！
Yeah!
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterflies, take flight!
舞い踊れよ
Dance away!
三千世界 コインシャワー
A shower of coins across the universe!
刹那を生きてよ
Live in the moment!
瞬間 クライマックス
Instant climax!
浮世忘れて
Forget the floating world,
耽る Dancing
Indulge in dancing!
ハイ ハイ ハイハイ 開演！
Hai, hai, hai, hai, curtain up!
ディスコ・ゴシック
Disco Gothic!
バイバイ仮面
Bye-bye mask!
ディスコ・ゴシック
Disco Gothic!
バイバイ仮面
Bye-bye mask!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあ、早速自己紹介からしていきましょうか！
Alright, let's jump right into our self-introductions!
していきましょう！
Let's do it!
じゃあ、みんなペコーラの久しぶりの挨拶いくから
Alright, I'm going to do my long-awaited greeting, everyone!
分かるよね、みんなー！あの挨拶だよ！
You all know it, right, everyone? That greeting!
あの挨拶だ！あれだ！
That greeting! That one!
あれしかない！
It can only be that one!
いくよー！
Here we go!
ドドンガドン ドン！
Dodonga-don don!
全人類Vチューバー... ん？
Vtuber of all mankind... wait, what?
そんな挨拶だったか？！
Was that really the greeting?!
大丈夫か？
Are you okay?
もう1回ね！もう1回ね！
One more time! One more time!
行きます！
Here I go!
ズン！
Zun!
ドドンガドン ドン！
Dodonga-don don!
全Vチューバー1超絶可愛いのは誰だー！？
Who is the super cute number one among all Vtubers?!
ドドンガドン ドン ドン！
Dodonga-don don don!
ぺこらー！
Pekora!
よく出来ましたー！
Well done!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃあ、次はフレアん！
Alright, next up is Flare-an!
はい！じゃあ、フレアは
Alright! Well, Flare,
『ハイダーリン』って言うので、『ハイハイー』って言って返してください！
will say "Hai, darling", so please call back with "Hai, hai"!
オッケー！
Okay!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
ハイダーリン！
Hai, darling!
ハイハイー！
Hai, hai!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
I'm Shiranui Flare from Hololive 3rd Generation!
そして...
And next...
はい！えー、どうしようかな？
Yes! Um, what should I do?
じゃあ『こんまっするー』って言うから、普通に『こんまっするー』で...
Well, I'll say "Kon-muscle", so please respond with "Kon-muscle"...
『牛丼』はいいのか？
Are you sure about skipping "Gyudon"?
牛丼もね！牛丼はまあ... バツ！
Gyudon too! Well, Gyudon is... no!
あ、やばいやばい！
Ah, oops!
あははは！よし、行こう！
Ahahaha! Alright, let's go!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
こんまっするー！
Kon-muscle!
はい、ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです！
Yes, I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd Generation!
よろしくねー！
Nice to meet you!
はい！
Alright!
そして...
And next...
きみたちー！
Everyone~!
本物のバイバイ仮面はだーれ！？
Who is the real Bye-bye Kamen?!
だーれ！？
Who is it?!
なんか割り切れないけど...
I'm not quite sure about that...
『バイバイ仮面』...！『バイバイ仮面』...！
"Bye-bye Kamen"...! "Bye-bye Kamen"...!
ねえ何でさー...
Hey, why is it...
ここに船長取られるし、ノエルにバイバイ仮面...
My spot here gets taken, and Noel gets Bye-bye Kamen...
本物ですか？
Are you the real one?
本物のバイバイ仮面が奪われたわけですね！
So the real Bye-bye Kamen was stolen from me!
あー、悲しい...
Ah, so sad...
ということでね
Anyway...
はい、ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Yes, I'm Houshou Marine, Captain of the Houshou Pirates, from Hololive 3rd Generation!
やー、ついにDay 2...
Ah, finally Day 2...
Day 2ですよ！Day 2！
It's Day 2! Day 2!
衣装違くない！？
Wait, aren't our outfits different?!
分かりましたか、皆さん！
Did you notice, everyone?!
ちょっと悪魔になっちゃった！
We've turned into devils a bit!
あら！天使から悪魔っぽくなってしまったかな？
My! Did we go from angels to devilish?
そうなんですよねー！
That's right!
実はこれ、初めて公開するんですよねー！
Actually, this is the first time we're revealing this!
そうなんですよー！
That's right!
みんなびっくりしたかな？
I wonder if everyone was surprised?
可愛いー！ありがとうー！
So cute! Thank you!
え？でも悪魔... なんか結構...
Eh? But devils... actually...
マリンは小悪魔系で売ってるんで、かなりシナジーあるかな？
Marine sells herself as a little devil type, so maybe there's great synergy?
普段から小悪魔系って言ってるからね！
I always call myself a little devil type, after all!
何言ってんだ！何が小悪魔だ！
What are you talking about?! Little devil, where?!
悪魔... 悪魔だな！
Devil... yeah, a devil.
変な悪魔いらない！変な悪魔嫌だ！
We don't need weird devils! I don't want weird devils!
天使と悪魔、どっちが好きキミたち？
Angels or devils, which do you prefer, everyone?
あ、確かに！
Ah, good point!
じゃペンライト振ってもらえば！天使の色何色？
Then let's have them wave penlights! What color for angels?
天使は白かな？
Angels are white, maybe?
白と赤？
White and red?
色的にね！
Color-wise!
じゃあ、悪魔派は赤！赤！
Then the devil faction is red! Red!
天使派は白！白ね！
The angel faction is white! White!
じゃあ行くか！
Let's do it then!
じゃあ皆さん変えてください！
Alright, everyone please change your colors!
掲げてください！掲げてー！
Hold them up! Hold them up!
あ、でも結構いい感じに割れてる！
Ah, but it's pretty evenly split!
若干赤が多いか？赤が多い！
Is red slightly more? Red is more!
あれ？悪魔の方が人気...！？
Huh? Is the devil side more popular?!
あ、でも半々くらい！半々！
Ah, but it's about half and half! Half and half!
すげー！
Awesome!
えー、じゃあ今日いいね！悪魔な感じも！
So today is great! With the devilish vibe too!
これ見せられて良かったね！
Glad we got to show this!
そしてDay 1に引き続き、バンドも生演奏でお届けします！
And continuing from Day 1, the band will be performing live!
イェーイ！よろしくお願いしまーす！
Yay! Thank you so much!
衣装かっこいいですね
These costumes are so cool, aren't they?
かっこいい！ ありがとうございます！
So cool! Thank you so much!
嬉しいですね！ そしてね
We're so happy! And also...
配信のコメントももちろん見えてます！
Of course, we can see the stream comments too!
配信の皆さんも！
Everyone on the stream too!
もうもちろん会場の皆さんももちろん！
And of course, everyone here at the venue too!
みんな素敵な気合の入った推し活ファッションしてきてくれて
Thank you everyone for coming in such awesome fan gear!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
かわいい！
So cute!
最高ですよ！ 最高ですね！
You guys are the best! Absolutely the best!
初っ端ね、シャッフルメドレーでしたけど
Right from the start, we had the shuffle medley!
すごーい！ びっくりだったよね！
Amazing! That was such a surprise, right?
でもですね、なんとですね、ここまでで...
But, believe it or not, up until here...
冒頭無料チラ見せが終了となります！
...the free stream sneak peek comes to an end!
えー！？ 嘘でしょ！？ 嘘ぺこだ！
What!? No way! That's a lie-peko!
そうなんですね... 嘘ではないぺこだった...
That's right... It wasn't a lie-peko after all...
みんな見たいと思ってくれてると思うから
We know you all want to keep watching, so...
概要欄に配信チケットのリンクがあるので、今ポチポチっと買ってみてください！
Check the link in the description for stream tickets and buy yours right now!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
後悔はさせない！ 今日はすごい！
You won't regret it! Today is going to be amazing!
今日ね、ぶち上げぶち上げで！
Today is going to be super hyped up too!
Day1とは違ったね、盛り上がり！
A whole different level of excitement from Day 1!
君たちも今日超ぶち上がりなんで！
You guys are super hyped up today too!
頑張って最後まで息切れしないようにぶち上がってください！
Work hard and stay hyped all the way to the end without running out of breath!
最後までしっかり声出してね！
Make sure to shout loud until the very end!
配信で楽しんでる人はハッシュタグ「きゅるるん大作戦Day2」でいっぱい呟いてください！
If you're enjoying on stream, tweet lots using the hashtag "#きゅるるん大作戦Day2"!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
はーい！ じゃあそろそろ...
Alright! Now then, it's about time...
次の曲にいってもいいでしょうか？
Shall we move on to the next song?
次の曲はなんと私からスタートさせていただいて...
Believe it or not, the next song starts with me...
何が来るんですか！？ なんだろう？
What's coming up!? What could it be?
次の曲いきましょう！ フレアメドレー！
Let's go to the next song! Flare Medley!
イエーイ！
Yay!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!